(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T18:29:14.730896",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Amazing!
I feel amazing, and you guys need to look forward for the upcoming performance tonight!
I feel amazing, and you guys need to look forward to tonight's upcoming performance!
Yeah! Hahaha
Yeah! Haha!
Have fun, and please enjoy tonight show as well.
Have fun, and please enjoy tonight's show as well!
Thank you!
Okay, bye!
とても楽しみです。
I'm really looking forward to it.
実は このメンバーで一緒に歌うのは初めてになると思うので 全員で奏でるハーモニーにぜひぜひ注目してほしいです。
Actually, since this is my first time singing with this group, I really want you to notice our harmony.
キケリキー！キラちゃんお誕生日おめでとう！一緒にライブをすることができてとっても嬉しいです。
Kikerikī! Happy birthday, Kira-chan! I'm so happy we get to do a live together.
なので 見ているみんなも一緒に盛り上がってほしいな！
So I hope everyone watching gets hyped up with us too!
ということで最高の生誕ライブにしましょう！イェイ！
With that said, let's make this the best birthday live ever! Yay!
AZKiでした！
This was AZKi!
I feel so excited.
You know, I feel like me and Kiara have a lot of things in common about performance.
You know, I feel like me and Kiara have a lot in common regarding performances.
So singing and dancing, we really love doing that. We really love...
Singing and dancing—we really love doing that. We really love...
performs, and also...
performing, and also...
I think we have the same taste of genre.
I think we have the same taste in genres.
So singing with her and dancing with her in the same stage, I feel really, really happy,
So singing and dancing with her on the same stage, I feel really, really happy,
excited, and I can't wait to show you guys!
Hello KFP,
I hope you guys enjoy our performance, um...
I hope you guys enjoy our performance...
I hope you guys enjoy all the things in Kiara's anniversary.
I hope you guys enjoy all the things for Kiara's anniversary.
And don't forget to always support her, always buy her merch, and really loop her song!
And don't forget to always support her, always buy her merch, and loop her song!
Thank you!
Bye-bye! Thank you!
It's always a blast to be performing with Takanashi Kiara, so I hope you'll be looking forward to it as well.
It's always a blast to perform with Takanashi Kiara, so I hope you're looking forward to it too.
KFP, I hope you're all ready to have the night of your lives!
KFP, I hope you're all ready for the night of your lives!
Thank you so much for coming out today, everyone, and don't forget to cheer extra loud for the birthday girl, Kiara!
Happy birthday, Kiara! And uh, for now KFP, bye-bye!
Happy birthday, Kiara! And for now, KFP, bye-bye!
クールビューティー？ですかね？
Cool beauty? Is that it?
かっこよくて美しい僕たちのパフォーマンス楽しみにしていてください！
Please look forward to our cool and beautiful performances!
ハローキララチャンネル！ロボ子です！
Hello Kiara Channel! I'm Roboco!
とても感情をこめて歌って踊ったので、楽しみにしていてください。
I sang and danced with all my heart, so please look forward to it.
Please enjoy! Please... rook... wii!
Please enjoy! Please look... Wii!
イェイ！
Yay!
Thank you!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
How am I feeling about my upcoming performance tonight?
Oh, I believe we have cooked so hard.
And yeah, how much can I say?
Well, I do believe and I do sincerely hope you guys are going to enjoy it.
Because me, I have a really good feeling about this, all right? I'm so so happy.
Uh, I wonder... I wonder what.
You know, you guys need to keep treating Kiara right, okay? Keep treating her right, cuz, you know, she deserves it and it's her party night today.
You guys need to keep treating Kiara right, okay? Keep treating her right, 'cuz, you know, she deserves it and it's her party night today.
So you guys better shower her with lots of love, okay?
We're here to celebrate as well, but ultimately, yeah, celebrate for her. It's her day. Let's freaking go!
Thank you!
Bye-bye! Hope you guys enjoy!
きょ、きょ、きょ、でござる！
Ke-Ke-Keken, de gozaru!
ホロックスの用人坊、侍の風間いろはでござる。
Holox's bodyguard, samurai Kazama Iroha de gozaru!
Today's live show, um, I'm very nervous.
I practice hard so that I could give a performance that I would not be embarrassed this time next year. Senpai, totemo kinchou shite imasu.
I practiced hard so that I could give a performance that I would not be embarrassed this time next year. Senpai, totemo kinchou shite imasu.
But um, I'm happy to be a guest performer at Kiara-senpai's wonderful live show.
So we will bring our best singing and dancing. Please enjoy the show!
今日は楽しんでいってくださいでござる！
Today, please enjoy the show, de gozaru!
I'm super nervous and excited to perform with Kiara.
Our performance is going to be mind-blowing.
Kiara's amazing, and you guys are lucky to have her as your tenthil.
Kiara's amazing, and you guys are lucky to have her as your tenchou.
Thank you so much! Bye myys!
Oh, you know, I'm just so excited. I invited all my friends
to dance and perform with me today, and I practiced so hard, spilled so much sweat, sweaty spaghetti, you know?
Um, but I think the result will be really exquisite, divine, perhaps.
Oh yeah, um, of course, subscribe, like, leave a comment, all of that. Make sure to share it with your friends. Wink!
Thank you! Yay! Bye-bye, enjoy the show everybody! Bye!
またたく星の架け橋を
Connecting memories
かけたセリフを繋ぎ合わせたメモリー
of the twinkling star's bridge...
鮮やかな銃舎が伝う
Vibrant gunshot carries through
新聞の言葉に
the newspaper's words,
祈り耳耳を
listen closely
澄ませ
to the prayers...
Tell me I can hear it clearly,
Tell me 声なく光に
Tell me into the soundless light
あだぶる言葉　傷を焦がす
Double words scorch the wounds,
微笑みそっと空に　身をやつして
Gently disguise yourself in the smiling sky,
選ばれし赤は　バッデリー継承
The chosen red inherits the battery,
あまた重なる試練を　引き抜いてみせる
Pulling through countless overlapping trials,
アイはレッド　Keep on fighting直到咚
Love is red, Keep on fighting until done,
先の見えない　ゼロの境界
At the unseen zero boundary,
迷い込んだとしても　何度も繰り返される
Even if you wander in, it repeats over and over,
この終焉　そこに
this finale, right there.
瞬く星のゆりかご 欠けた台詞を
Cradle of twinkling stars, connecting
繋ぎ合わせたメモリア
broken lines of memory.
聖なる従者が言い伝える神話の理
The sacred follower tells of mythic truths,
祈りに耳を澄ませば
so listen closely to the prayer.
tell me, i can hear it clearly
tell me, 声なき声に
tell me, to a voiceless voice,
荒ぶる鼓動は弱さを焦がす
raging heartbeats scorch away weakness.
炎降り注ぐ空 身をやつして
Yielding my body to falling skies of flame,
乱れ咲く赤は紅化粧
blooming in disarray, red makeup adorns.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみる
Surviving countless trials and tribulations,
i will live to keep on fighting 'til the dawn
たとえば先の見えない零の境界
Even if at the unseen boundary of zero,
迷い込んだとしても
getting lost within it all,
何度も繰り返される孤高の終焉
endless repetition of a solitary end,
そこに残ったanswer
the answer left behind there.
don't break, i will never give up
don't break, 羽が朽ちても
don't break, even if my wings decay,
消せない強さは時の導
unfading strength is the guide of time.
灰花舞い上がる大地 身をくぐらせ
Ground where ash flowers dance up, passing through,
燃える朱の中目を覚ます
awakening amidst the burning crimson eyes.
刃交わる 切っ先交わした契りは
Promises crossed at blade's tip,
lies and truth, come to light at the break of day
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me astray
if i go wrong, what awaits me in the dark?
could you tell me please, where i need to go?
tell me, i can hear it clearly
tell me, 声なき声に
tell me, to a voiceless voice,
澄まる決意は闇夜を晴らす
resolute determination clears the dark night.
炎降り注ぐ空 身をやつして
Yielding my body to falling skies of flame,
乱れ咲く赤は紅化粧
blooming in disarray, red makeup adorns.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみる
Surviving countless trials and tribulations,
blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
and in the next life too, i promise i will find you
Kikkirikiki!
we're so back, welcome to my 4th anniversary 3D live!
That was Hinotori Redshift Remix, the first time I ever performed this version of it.
Did you like the comeback of the kikkiriki?
Well, well, well, let me take you through the stage a little bit, this is our new stage!
It looks so luxurious and beautiful, wow, so shiny, I know!
We also have a very, or I have a very special surprise for you guys at the end of this live.
The last song, what could it be? It will still stay a surprise, but please still stay until the very end.
And we have many guests too, that you may already have seen or heard about, so look forward to them!
Yeah, the next song will be a cover song from Kiara, my song, even though, you know, similar vibe to my original songs.
So please enjoy, Nice Type!
it’s getting dark out here so watch your back, pay attention now
a demon on the loose, i’m co-co-coming for you now
watching and teasin’
make it so easy
deception, here’s a lesson
baby why don’t you give in
the feeling
you want it
you need it
go get it dreamin’
believe it
take control
you’re just so
so easy
i can’t stop
i’m greedy
satisfy the hunger got you lock-locked down
still beggin’ for more
sinister allure
no clue what you got yourself into at all, caught ya, escalate it
no more runnin’ now
boy i could blow your
try if you want
i’ll let you come inside my mind
hold it down and let’s go all night
oh you look so nervous what’s wrong don’t be polite
got you on your knees
i never claimed to be the nice type
intentionally innocent to you
you lookin’ round for help but ain’t no use
boy you shoulda known once i’m done i’m movin’ on
one look into my eyes you’re gonna fold
you’re mine forever but i ain’t yours no
it only takes a minute
to get you all addicted
you can’t ever get enough oh no no no
still beggin’ for more
sinister allure
no clue what you got yourself into at all, caught ya, escalate it
no more runnin’ now
boy i’m gonna blow your
I miss you
Didn't want to admit it, but I do
Always been close, but far away
You go, but then you stay, yeah, that's always been you
I guess we are different after all
But it's shocking how far apart we grew
So I cut all the ties to play it safe, but you like playing games
It's always been you
And somehow you're still here
This feeling could kill me
Somehow you're still here
And this might take me out, take me down, take me apart
Oh, I got it bad, got attached, my imagination
Brings me right back to you
Always want it all, when I fall, I fall hard, oh baby
Tell me why, tell me why
Tell me, why does a heart break, a heart break, a heart?
Tell me, why does a heart break, the stars fade?
Oh baby, tell me why, tell me why
It's kinda painful to tell the truth
I should cry it out, but I don't usually do
Some things don't change though, I'd make them if I could
'Cause I don't feel human, I wonder if you would
And it's not even fair that you're happy with her
And you're so unaware, maybe that's why it hurts?
The world stops, and the clock keeps ticking all night
Oh, I got it bad, got attached, my imagination
Brings me right back to you
Always want it all, when I fall, I fall hard, oh baby
Tell me why, tell me why
Tell me, why does a heart...
Why won't you let me go?
I really wanna really be alone
Delete my number from your phone
I want to be alone
But somehow you're still here
Somehow you're, you're still here
And this might take me out, take me down, take me apart
Oh, I got it bad, got attached, my imagination
Brings me right back to you
Always want it all, when I fall, I fall hard, oh baby
Tell me why, tell me why
Oh, I got it bad, got attached, my imagination
Brings me right back to you
Always want it all, when I fall, I fall hard, oh baby
Tell me why, tell me why
Tell me, why does a heart break, a heart break, a heart?
Tell me, why does a heart break, the stars fade?
Oh baby, tell me why, tell me why
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
We can't wait to talk!
I know, right!
I returned!
Thank you so much for fighting with me.
Of course! It's such a rare duo.
I know, right!
We had to do it.
I think this is the first time we sang and danced together like just the two of us.
Did you like it?
Did you guys like it?
Introduce yourself then!
Hiwis! It's IRyS from Hololive English Promise!
Yeah!
And I am just so so happy.
Me too!
I think I've been in Hololive for like over three years, and I just can't believe this is our first time.
I think I've been in Hololive for over three years, and I can't believe this is our first time.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yeah, yeah, no, I know, it's very special, so.
Yeah, yeah, I know. It's very special, so.
Yeah, it was a really special song, too, right?
Yeah! Why does a heartbreak... Yo, why does a heartbreak, IRyS?
Ah, I mean, technically I've never been heartbroken ever in my life. No?
Ah, I mean, technically I've never been heartbroken ever in my life.
What about me? Well...
I mean, I might have broken her heart, but I've never been broken.
Well, I mean, honestly when we were doing this dance move...
I sniffed, I sniffed, huh? Oh! I smell pee on you!
Liars! It was your boyfriend last night!
No, no, I was alone last night! What are you talking about?
She's lying. She's a fat liar. Was it a night before?
She's lying, she's a fat liar! Was it the night before?
Maybe she was a fat liar right now. Was it a night before?
Maybe she's a fat liar right now! Was it the night before?
No! If you see, I wash my hair every day! It smells like your whole body...
No! Look, I wash my hair every day! It smells like your whole body...
Exudes the... Okay! Wow!
Well, let me let me take a sniff at your hair, you know?
Mmm, ah, it smells nice. It smells a little bit like a nice smelling crow.
Mmm, ah, it smells nice. It smells a little bit like a nice-smelling crow.
A crow? Maybe like... That could be Kronii, too?
No, Kronii is not a crow! I'm thinking someone like the Nerissa, right?
No, Kronii is not a crow! I'm thinking someone like Nerissa, right?
Nerissa! Nerissa! Well, I mean, honestly that could be, because me and Nerissa, I thought we had, you know, something, because I felt like she... You do have something. Thank you!
Well, I got a little bit confused because a while ago at the New York concert, she was kissed, okay? She didn't kiss her. She was kissed by Shiori.
Huh? So now I'm really confused because I know she loves Shiori and then I'm like, where do I stand with her? I'm so confused.
I mean, no, you guys just take your relationship, especially when it comes to kissing and stuff, more personal, not like in private, I'm assuming, right?
Did you guys like take a shower together? No, no, we were in swimsuits.
Okay, okay. I think I'll clear it up with her because the song after this...
I think I sense her presence.
Oh yeah, maybe you should talk to her a bit if you're worried, you know? She's Nerissa, so you know, we should go on a like couple date.
Oh yeah, maybe you should talk to her a bit if you're worried, you know? She's Nerissa, so you know, we should go on a couple of dates.
No, no, not a couple date, it's just a group of friends. What are you talking about? It's just a group of friends.
No, not a couple date! It's just a group of friends. What are you talking about? It's just a group of friends.
Well then, Are you guys ready for the next song? I am so excited to see that! Thank you! All right, you watch on the sidelines. See you guys, next song!
幾つの苦も美美主義
With numerous hardships, an aesthetic philosophy,
愛の反戦 一人じゃんけん
Anti-war of love, playing rock-paper-scissors alone.
運命と縛り見ない振り それも暗転
Feigning ignorance of fate's bonds, even that blacks out.
Now I know all about you babe
I don't want the handbags the money or the diamond rings
'Cause guys like you they all don't care about the little things
'Cause guys like you, you all don't care about the little things.
まぁ anyway 吹っ切れた訳で
Well, anyway, I've gotten over it.
棒に当たって吠えたって圏外です
Barking up the wrong tree is out of bounds.
I'm moving on and I'm never ever turning back around, around, around again
Now I'll go higher and I'll go higher
And you couldn't take me down if you tried
ばら撒いてた愛 取り返し撤退だ
Taking back the love I scattered, it's a retreat.
Now I can finally open my eyes
そんで来世もっかい 君への返品サイン
Then in the next life too, returning my sign to you.
Getcha out my life boy I'll getcha, getcha, getcha!
待ちっ恋なんて 錠をかけキー捨て去って
Waiting on love, lock it up and throw away the key.
'Cause I'm fine, I'm alright 君なしで大正解 Getcha out my life boy I'll getcha, getcha, getcha!
'Cause I'm fine, I'm alright, without you it's the right choice. Getcha out my life, boy! I'll getcha, getcha, getcha!
(Getcha out my life boy, get out my life boy)
(Getcha out my life boy, I'll getcha, getcha, getcha!)
Oops! Deleted your number
All of my friends used to warn me about ya
Baby, I thought that i couldn't without ya
I got myself now i don't need no other
もう息も止まるときめきすら ない今
Now, even the heartbeat that stops my breath is gone.
酸素吸ってはいいちょう泳いでくlike na nana na na
Inhaling oxygen, swimming through like na nana na na.
I don't want the handbags the money or the diamond rings
'Cause guys like you they all don't care about the little things
'Cause guys like you, you all don't care about the little things.
そう everyday 自己愛は順調で 先手打ち勝ち賞金掠めて bye babe
Yes everyday self-love is going smoothly, seizing the prize money beforehand, bye babe.
I'm moving on and I'm never ever turning back around, around, around again
Now I'll go higher and I'll go higher
And you couldn't take me down if you tried
ばら撒いてた愛 取り返し撤退だ Now I can finally open my eyes
Taking back the love I scattered, it's a retreat. Now I can finally open my eyes.
幾つもの苦も美意識主義
Countless hardships are an aesthetic philosophy,
愛の反戦一人じゃんけん
anti-war of love, playing rock-paper-scissors alone.
運命と縛り見ない振りの
Feigning ignorance of fate and bonds,
それも暗転
that too turns to blackout.
Now I know all about you babe
I don't want the handbags, the money or the diamond rings
'Cause guys like you they all don't care about the little things
まぁ anyway 吹っ切れた筈で
Well, anyway, I should've moved on,
棒に当たって砕けてた圏外です
hitting a post, shattered and out of bounds.
I'm moving on and I'm never ever turning back around, around, around again
break!
隠してた偽造id
Hiding a forged ID,
暴落した価値 four on knees
collapsed value, four on knees.
円滑な生活 reigns
Smooth life reigns,
流されてけ スライダー outta way
washed away, slider outta way.
盲目な愛が溶けてくアイス バー
Blind love melting like an ice bar,
もろく砕け泡が抜けたソーダ
fragilely broken, soda with gone bubbles.
からっけだ no pressure
Empty, no pressure,
Not to press ya, I'll getcha
ばら撒いていた愛 取り返し撤退だ
The love I scattered is a refund and retreat,
Now I can finally open my eyes
そんで来世もっかい君への返品サイン
and then in the next life once more, return sign to you.
Getcha out my life boy
I'll getcha, getcha, getcha
待ちっびなしの恋なんて
A love that leaves you waiting forever,
錠をかけキー捨て去って
put a lock on it and throw away the key.
'Cause I'm fine, I'm alright
君なしで大正解
without you it's the right choice.
Getcha out my life boy
I'll getcha, getcha, getcha
待ちぼうけと恋なんて
Waiting and love like that...
じっくり傷つけてさいて
hurts deeply and tears apart.
今までにない
Never before,
待ちわびた最終回
the long-awaited final episode.
Getcha out my life boy
I'll getcha, getcha, getcha
All the lies and every mistake
All the goodbyes and the heartbreak
枯れ切った涙さえ
Even the dried-up tears,
no more
break!
気付いたんだ 今は rollin'
I realized now is rollin'
止まりたくないんだ no need
I don't want to stop, no need.
分かってんだ 魅せられたからって
I know, just because I was charmed,
雑な罠に嵌まるつもりなど無い
I have no intention of falling into a sloppy trap.
当たり前が止まんない 怖いな
The obvious won't stop, how scary,
もどかしさも正しい命題
frustration is also a correct proposition.
ハロー 湧いてくる束の間の自負心
Hello, fleeting self-pride wells up,
そこからはどう見えてる? tell me, tell me
How does it look from there? tell me, tell me.
どれだけ僕を救ってくれるの
How much can you save me?
反応していく声 加速して
Responding voices accelerating,
始まりは何処から? それも容赦無い力
Where did it start? That merciless power too.
身体を支配している 満ち足りた意欲
Governing my body, fulfilled ambition.
darlin' darlin' タフに噛んでいくスタイル
darlin' darlin' a style of chewing toughly,
まびまび 幕を上げるのさ
slowly raising the curtain.
何がどうなったって不思議じゃない
It's no wonder whatever happens,
振りが増し 答えになって響き出すよ
Gestures increase, echoing as the answer.
come over 消えていかない感覚
come over, a sensation that doesn't fade,
飽きる迄踊ってたいいだけ
I just want to dance until I'm bored.
気付いたんだ 今は rollin'
I realized now is rollin'
止まりたくないんだのにな
I don't want to stop, yet...
やばい 何となく なのに
Oh no, somehow, yet
見透かされてるのに
I'm being seen right through.
予想より横着で長い傾向
A tendency longer and lazier than expected,
不確かなものに囲まれてるんだね
Surrounded by uncertain things, aren't we?
そこらじゅうに転がってる堕落妄想
Cowardly delusions rolling everywhere,
だと思ってほか重要 心に逆らう外れまった振る舞い
Behavior straying against the heart.
気付いたんだ 今は rollin'
I realized now is rollin'
止まりたくないんだのに
I don't want to stop, yet
やばい 何となく なのに
Oh no, somehow, yet
見透かされてるのに
Seen right through.
予想より横着で長い傾向
A tendency longer and lazier than expected,
不確かなものに囲まれてるんだね
Surrounded by uncertain things, aren't we?
そこらじゅうに転がってる堕落妄想
Cowardly delusions rolling everywhere,
だと思ってほか重要 心に逆らう外れまった振る舞い
Behavior straying against the heart.
どれだけ僕を救ってくれるの
How much can you save me?
反応していく声 加速して
Responding voices accelerating,
始まりは何処から? それも容赦無い力
Where did it start? That merciless power too.
身体を支配している 満ち足りた意欲
Governing my body, fulfilled ambition.
darlin' darlin' タフに噛んでいくスタイル
darlin' darlin' a style of chewing toughly,
まびまび 幕を上げるのさ
Slowly raising the curtain.
何がどうなったって不思議じゃない
It's no wonder whatever happens,
振りが増し 答えになって響き出すよ
Gestures increase, echoing as the answer.
come over 消えていかない感覚
Come over, a sensation that doesn't fade,
飽きる迄踊ってたいいだけ
I just want to dance until I'm bored.
気付いたんだ 今は rollin'
I realized now is rollin'
止まりたくないんだ no need
I don't want to stop, no need.
分かってんだ 魅せられたからって
I know, just because I was charmed,
雑な罠に嵌まるつもりなど無い
I have no intention of falling into a sloppy trap.
当たり前が止まんない 怖いな
The obvious won't stop, how scary,
もどかしさも正しい命題
Frustration is also a correct proposition.
ハロー 湧いてくる束の間の自負心
Hello, fleeting self-pride wells up,
そこからはどう見えてる? tell me, tell me
How does it look from there? tell me, tell me.
どれだけ僕を救ってくれるの
How much can you save me?
反応していく声 加速して
Responding voices accelerating,
始まりは何処から? それも容赦無い力
Where did it start? That merciless power too.
身体を支配している 満ち足りた意欲
Governing my body, fulfilled ambition.
darlin' darlin' タフに噛んでいくスタイル
darlin' darlin' a style of chewing toughly,
まびまび 幕を上げるのさ
Slowly raising the curtain.
何がどうなったって不思議じゃない
It's no wonder whatever happens,
振りが増し 答えになって響き出すよ
Gestures increase, echoing as the answer.
come over 消えていかない感覚
Come over, a sensation that doesn't fade,
飽きる迄踊ってたいいだけ
I just want to dance until I'm bored.
気付いんだ 今は rollin' 止まりたくないんだ no need
Opened my eyes to see that I’m rollin'
Don’t wanna stop, because there’s no need
分かってんだ 魅せられたからって 雑な罠に嵌まるつもり無い
Now I see it, my fascination entranced me
Don’t let that make you believe that I’m fallin'
当たり前が止まらない 怖いな もどかしさも 正しい命題
Living mundanely, the thought’s enough to scare me
It’s too frustrating to wonder if life will bounce back
ハロー 湧いてくる 東の間の自負心 そこからはどう見えてる？ tell me, tell me
Hello to this sense of pride that suddenly I see
How does it look from your own eyes? Tell me, tell me
どれだけ僕を救ってくれるのか 反応していく声 加速して
When will you adorn your cape and rush to save me?
Channel those echoing voices and play them at top speed
始まりは 何処 から？ それ も容赦無い力 身体を支配している
Where did we make our brand new starting?
I feel this power growing within
満ち足りた意欲
Now I can feel my body brimming with ambition
Hey!
やったよ！ やってできました！ 合作！
We did it! We successfully did a collab!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Hey! いろはちゃん、Welcome!
Hey Iroha-chan, welcome!
Introduction, please!
ハロー！ My name is 風真いろは！ Japaneseホロライブ6期生
Hello! My name is Kazama Iroha!
Hololive Japan 6th Generation
ホロックスの... よろしくお願いします！
HoloX... Please treat me well!
Welcome! やった！ いろはちゃん！
Welcome! Yay, Iroha-chan!
We sang Beat Eater together. I'm so happy because...
I really, really love this song. And when I chose it, I thought...
I need someone who can dance really well, which is いろはちゃん！
I need someone who can dance really well, which is Iroha-chan!
But then I, I after like I already chose you, I realized when I was looking up Beat Eater on YouTube,
But after I already chose you, I realized when I was looking up Beat Eater on YouTube,
I found your cover! I was like, "Eh? She sang it already?!"
Yes! もうカバーしてる！
Yes! I already covered it!
そうなんです！ そう、だから今回誘ってもらえて
That's right! So, that's why when you invited me this time,
とってもとっても嬉しくて！ ソ、Beat Eater、そ、Very very pop and cool, so I love it so... Thank you!
I was so, so happy! So Beat Eater is very, very pop and cool, so I love it... Thank you!
I love it! Thank you today! はい、Thank you!
I love it! Thank you today! Yeah, thank you!
ありがとうございます！ ライブゲスト、Thank you！ ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Live guest, thank you! Thank you very much!
Well, it was a very like dance-focused song, so I wonder what dance move was difficult for you?
やっぱり、サビ！ サビ！
As expected, the chorus! The chorus!
つつ、つ、つ、つ、つーて、て、て、て、てー... So waving, so very difficult, so...
Tsu-tsu, tsu, tsu, tsu, tsu-te, te, te, te, te-... So waving, so very difficult, so...
Actually, I also just, like, today I finally understood. 今日、やっと把握できた。
Actually, I also just... Today I finally understood it.
今日だからリハーサル、そ、一緒に、そ、レッスン、ん？ ん？
Today at rehearsal, right, together, right, lessons, hmm? Hmm?
ディスエイブル、ん？ 今日できたこと、やりましたもんね！
Disabled, hmm? We did what we could do today, right!
For me, there's like, you know, when I overthink, overthinking, then I like forget how to do the simplest things,
For me, you know, when I overthink, overthinking, then I like forget how to do the simplest things,
even though I know that I know it. So, there was this one move...
You like step forward, and when you step, you like kick the other leg back, right? And then you put it to the front and we add the hand, right? So it's like this. But I overthink and I like stumble and...
Step, kick, wave, more, more... (laughs) ...more resource. So I had to do it 100 times so that I stopped overthinking.
Step, kick, wave, more, more... more resource. So I had to do it 100 times so that I stopped overthinking.
Oh my god! But, but Kiara-san was practicing so hard!
いろはちゃんも！ そう、一緒に、そ、練習して、very fun!
Iroha-chan too! Right, practicing together, very fun!
Yes! ありがとう！ 楽しかった！
Yes! Thank you! It was fun!
本当に嬉しかった！ ありがとうございました！
I was so happy! Thank you very much!
Let's do it again sometime. Yes! Let's! So singing, dancing, some games together, yes!
Also, Iroha-chan, very nice English!
雑魚雑魚English! No, no, very nice English! マジ助かる、助かる！
Zako-zako English! No, no, very nice English! Seriously helps, helps!
More English practice. Hard, がんばります！
More English practice. Hard, I'll do my best!
OK! Shall with that, we move on to the next song...
OK! With that, we move on to the next song...
And the next guest, who could it be?! Bye-bye guys! See you next song! Bye-bye! Next guest! Yeah!
腹捻ってりゃ数年ポシャった この怠惰が憎いが まだこうしてベッドでまた寝腐っている
I wasted years rotting away, hating this laziness of mine
Still lying around in bed, rotting away once again
最近調子は悪いが いや本気はまだまだ そう言ったのは これで何回目の台詞だろ
Lately my condition's been bad, but no, my true power is still yet to come
How many times have I said that line already?
無造作なヘアー 一重の目尻 学歴は中の下で ご存じモテない 身なりは三流 お涙をどうそ御馳走様
Messy hair, single eyelids, below-average grades
Unpopular as you know, third-rate appearance, please enjoy these tears
僕等、優等生じゃない sa だだから終身刑でい～や
We aren't honor students, sa
So a life sentence is fine, i~ya
ノー天気 style い～やい～やい～やい～や
Carefree style, i~ya i~ya i~ya i~ya
金環際一生ナンセンスだってい～や
Even if it's total nonsense forever, i~ya
ノー天気 style い～やい～やい～やい～や
Carefree style, i~ya i~ya i~ya i~ya
最低で結構堂々クズでい～や
The worst is fine, proudly being scum is fine, i~ya
夜、センチメンタル相まって 自殺願望のロケットを 百四十文字のポエムに放っている
At night, sentimentality builds up, launching a rocket of suicidal desire
Into a 140-character poem
こりゃそうとーにbadきめきった なら寝言に決まった ただいつまでこうしてやり過ごすつもりだろ
This is totally bad, so it must be sleep-talking
Just how long do I plan on coasting by like this?
負け犬ほえる犬も同等
A losing dog, a barking dog is the same
今宵も当然 逃げ足だけが得意のゲーム
Naturally, escape is my specialty tonight, a game.
明日を待つのみ 口だけじゃしゃあねぇ
Just waiting for tomorrow, talking big won't cut it.
嘘も方便だって言うっしょ
They say a little lie never hurts, right?
だから道場なんていや
So a dojo or whatever is just no good.
嘘も方便だって言うっしょ
They say a little lie never hurts, right?
だから道場なんていや
So a dojo or whatever is just no good.
ノウ天気スタイル いやいやいや
Carefree style, no no no,
ゴールまで一緒 ぽんこつだっていいや
Together to the goal, being a clutz is fine!
ノウ天気スタイル いやいやいや
Carefree style, no no no,
最低限でけっこう ヒッピーだっていいや
Bare minimum is fine, being a hippie is fine!
腹減ったらやる気失った またスマホいじってた
Hungry and unmotivated, messing with my phone again.
ただこうしてベッドで死んだふりをしている
Just playing dead in bed like this.
言葉ったら一緒口んだ ならどうしてそうしない
Words are easy, so why don't you do it?
それはぼくがぼっちのヘテロだからだろ
Probably because I'm a lonely hetero.
また王座の椅子がバズった 正直痺れた
The throne's seat went viral again, honestly it thrilled me.
ただこうしてベッドで僕は重なっている
Just piling up in bed like this.
最近調子は悪いが いや本気はまだまだ
My condition's been bad lately, but my real power's still ahead.
東に西にもなってくれお釈迦様
Become east and west for me, Buddha!
ノウ天気スタイル いやいやいや
Carefree style, no no no,
郡山一緒フライボードでいいや
Together to Koriyama on a flyboard is fine!
ノウ天気スタイル いやいやいや
Carefree style, no no no,
最低限でけっこう 濃厚な汁だしていいや
Bare minimum is fine, releasing thick broth is fine!
ノウ天気スタイル
Carefree style...
あすは頑張ってといいな
Saying "Do your best tomorrow" is nice.
ノウ天気スタイル
Carefree style...
だから今日はくらっていいや
So getting beaten today is fine too.
Have more men?
Why did we fall asleep?
Oh, it's such a chill song, huh.
Ina!
How are you? Hello.
Uh, maybe you should introduce yourself.
Myself?
Hi!
I'm Ina, the Smol English Myth! Hello!
Yeah, okay. I know it's comfortable on the floor. You love the floor.
Special floor, right? Floor rating? A solid 8.37!
Oh, that's really good. But we gotta leave the floor now. Guys, it's been so long since we released this as a song cover...
And now we finally performed it! Yeah, it's been a bit, like, three years? Over three years already!
Yeah!
Have you guys listened to it before, or are you a newcomer and you never heard it before? In that case, what should they do, Ina?
Listen to it! Listen to it! Yeah, but it's pretty far down.
So you gotta go to the videos and to Most Popular, because it's really popular! Yeah! Thank you, Takanashi!
Thank you for giving us love! And thanks for inviting me!
Of course, Ina! It's so fun with you. Oh yeah, we had that special dance.
Guys, dance with us! (robot dance noises) Yeah, robot, kind of. But it's like, ah whatever, whatever. Yeah, that's fine.
So, actually, this stage is like pretty like epic and god-like, isn't it? I feel like a goddess. So far, the songs haven't quite fit the theme, but now, in the second part of this...
There's going to be more guests, more songs, and they're all gonna fit the vibe. They're going to be god-like and epic. Yes! So, I'm kind of nervous. You can't wait?
Well, can you give me some kind of like motivation call, please, Ina? (Ina: "Eh? Eiya, eiya?") No, not whatever! Okay, okay. Well, just this time, okay? Okay, you're gonna join me on the oshi. Everyone will join me on the oshi, okay? On the oshi! Okay, sounds good. Here we go.
Takanashi! Fight! Fight! Fight! Never heard that before? Okay, okay! Thank you, everybody! Next song!
STYX HELIX
[Song: STYX HELIX]
Oh, please don't let me die
Waiting for your touch
No, don't give up on life
This endless dead end
狂った時計 刻む 命
A twisted clock tracks my remaining life,
こぼれていく 記憶 の 砂
a sand of memories spilling forth.
芽生え た 想い まで
Will even the feelings I developed
ねえ こんなにも呆気なく
so simply and foolishly
消えてしまう の
fade away?
I wish I was there
Oh, please don't let me die
Waiting for your touch
二度と 何も 失わぬ ように
So that I'll never lose anything again,
私 を 忘れて 初めて " restart "
I'll forget myself and "restart" from the beginning.
No, don't give up on life
This endless dead end
君 を 砕く この 悲しみ が
I hope that the sadness crushing you
いつか 終わり ますように
will someday end.
For now I 'll see you off
For now I'll see you off.
My time is spinning around
Your deep black eyes
I forgot what time it is
And our memories are gone...?
甘い 香り 放つ
Releasing a sweet fragrance
追憶 という 名 の 罠
are the traps of my memories.
誘わ れ 囚わ れ
They beckon and seize,
なぜ 抗い も せ ず また
and yet again, I'm unable to resist
溺れ て しまう の
and drown in them.
I wish you were here
Oh, never close your eyes
Searching for a true fate
どこか 消えた あの ぬくもり を
The warmth that disappeared somewhere
追いかけ 続けて 見失う " restart "
I keep chasing and lose sight of, "restart".
So, let us try again
From the very first time
" きっと きっと " そうやって 今 も
"Surely, surely" even now
虚しい 輪 を 描い ている
we are drawing a hollow ring.
For now, see you again
fading in, fading out
あの 日々 に は 戻れ ない
I can never go back to those days.
時 は 強く 哀しく 強く
Time is powerful, sad and powerful,
ただただ 進んで ゆく だけ " restart "
I can only keep proceeding forward, "restart".
No, don't give up on life
This endless dead end
振り返らない そんな強さを
The strength to never look back,
誰も誰も演じている
everyone is playing that role.
For now I 'll see you off
For now I'll see you off.
And we 'll die
And we'll die
Waiting for a new day
二度と...
Never again...
And we 'll start
And we'll start
Waiting for a new day
君と...
with you...
Oh, please don't let me die
消えないで ah...
don't let me fade away ah...
いつか君が瞳に灯す
The light of love that you will someday kindle in your eyes
愛の光が時を超えて
will transcend time,
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を 確実に一つ壊すだろう
And will surely destroy one dream of this world hurrying to ruin.
躇いを飲み干して
Swallowing down your hesitation,
君が望むモノは何?
What is it that you wish for?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
儚い明日はあるの?
does a transient tomorrow exist?
子どもの頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように
that I dreamed of when I was a child,
闇さえ砕く力で
With a power that can shatter even the darkness,
微笑みに会いたい
I want to meet you and your smile.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の勇気
is the courage of plucked flowers;
想いだけが頼る全て
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon.
光を
A wish
呼び覚ます
that awakens
願い
the light.
いつか君も誰かの為に
Someday, you will also wish for great power
強い力を望むのだろう
for the sake of someone else, I suppose.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
In the night when love captured your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれてくる
unknown words are born.
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can go on without losing my way,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I don't mind if my heart is broken to pieces.
いつも目の前の悲しみに
I want a spell to stand up against
立ち向かう為の呪文が欲しい
the sorrow that is always in front of my eyes.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are a memory that still dreams,
私は眠らない明日
I am the sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を
I will move forward in order to win
勝ち取る為に進むわ
the miracle of the two of us meeting.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の刃
is the blade of plucked flowers;
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
心に振りかざす 願い
A wish that I brandish within my heart.
囚われた太陽の輝く
When I used to like books of strange lands,
不思議の国が好きだった頃
illuminated by captive suns,
願いはきっと叶えると
I believed the fairy tales that taught us
教えるお伽話を信じた
that wishes would surely come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Gently, the ancient magic
古の魔法優しく
that was blooming wildly in silence
世界を変える力が
whispers that the power to change the world
その手にあると叫ぶ
lies in those hands of yours.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let us dream an unending dream
君と行く時の中で
during the time I go with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
命を作るのは 願い
What creates life is a wish.
いつか君も誰かの為に
Someday, you will also wish for great power
強い力を望むのだろう
for the sake of someone else, I suppose.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
In the night when love captured your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれてくる
unknown words are born.
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can go on without losing my way,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I don't mind if my heart is broken to pieces.
いつも目の前の悲しみに
I want a spell to stand up against
立ち向かう為の呪文が欲しい
the sorrow that is always in front of my eyes.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are a memory that still dreams,
私は眠らない明日
I am the sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を
I will move forward in order to win
勝ち取る為に進むわ
the miracle of the two of us meeting.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の刃
is the blade of plucked flowers;
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
心に振りかざす 願い
A wish that I brandish within my heart.
囚われた太陽の輝く
When I used to like books of strange lands,
不思議の国が好きだった頃
illuminated by captive suns,
願いはきっと叶えると
I believed the fairy tales that taught us
教えるお伽話を信じた
that wishes would surely come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Gently, the ancient magic
古の魔法優しく
that was blooming wildly in silence
世界を変える力が
whispers that the power to change the world
その手にあると叫ぶ
lies in those hands of yours.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let us dream an unending dream
君と行く時の中で
during the time I go with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
命を作るのは 願い
What creates life is a wish.
いつか君が瞳に灯す
The light of love that you will someday kindle in your eyes
愛の光が時を超えて
will transcend time,
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を 確実に一つ壊すだろう
And will surely destroy one dream of this world hurrying to ruin.
躇いを飲み干して
Swallowing down your hesitation,
君が望むモノは何?
What is it that you wish for?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
儚い明日はあるの?
does a transient tomorrow exist?
子どもの頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように
that I dreamed of when I was a child,
闇さえ砕く力で
With a power that can shatter even the darkness,
微笑みに会いたい
I want to meet you and your smile.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Gently, the ancient magic
古の魔法優しく
that was blooming wildly in silence
世界を変える力が
whispers that the power to change the world
その手にあると囁く
lies in those hands of yours.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let us dream an unending dream
君と行く時の中で
during the time I go with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
命を作るのは 願い
What creates life is a wish.
いつか君も誰かの為に
Someday, you will also wish for great power
強い力を望むのだろう
for the sake of someone else, I suppose.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
In the night when love captured your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれてくる
unknown words are born.
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can go on without losing my way,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I don't mind if my heart is broken to pieces.
いつも目の前の悲しみに 立ち向かう為の呪文が欲しい
I want a spell to stand up against...
ich möchte stärker werden,
I want to be stronger,
weil unsere welt sehr grausam ist
because our world is very cruel.
es ist ratsam, welke blumen zu entfernen
It is wise to remove withered flowers.
du fragst mich, ob ich mit dir komm
You ask me if I'll come with you,
du flüsterst mir in mein ohr
you whisper into my ear.
du fragst mich, ob ich deine hand nehm
You ask me if I'll take your hand,
ich hab keinen grund, dich abzulehnen
I have no reason to reject you.
du fragst mich, ob ich mit dir komm
You ask me if I'll come with you,
du flüsterst mir in mein ohr
you whisper into my ear.
du fragst mich, ob ich deine hand nehm
You ask me if I'll take your hand...
du fragst mich, ob ich mit dir komm
You ask me if I'll come with you,
du flüsterst mir in mein ohr
you whisper into my ear.
du fragst mich, ob ich deine hand nehm
You ask me if I'll take your hand,
du flüsterst mir
you whisper to me.
ja, ich bin viel stärker, als ich je gedacht hab
Yes, I am much stronger than I ever thought!
fliege höher!
Fly higher!
laufe viel schneller!
Run much faster!
vergiß die wahrheit nicht!
Do not forget the truth!
ja, ich bin viel stärker, als ich je gedacht hab
Yes, I am much stronger than I ever thought!
ich entferne welke blumen
I remove withered flowers.
wieso siehst du so traurig aus?
Why do you look so sad?
diese welt ist grausam
This world is cruel,
es ist traurig aber wahr
it is sad but true.
diese welt ist seltsam
This world is strange,
es ist fraglich aber wahr
it is questionable but true.
ist der blumengarten echt oder falsch?
Is the flower garden real or fake?
ich möchte stärker werden,
I want to be stronger,
weil unsere welt sehr grausam ist
because our world is very cruel.
es ist ratsam, welke blumen zu entfernen
It is wise to remove withered flowers.
du fragst mich, ob ich mit dir komm
You ask me if I'll come with you,
du flüsterst mir in mein ohr
you whisper into my ear.
ja, ich bin viel stärker, als ich je gedacht hab
Yes, I am much stronger than I ever thought!
fliege höher!
Fly higher!
laufe viel schneller!
Run much faster!
vergiß die wahrheit nicht!
Do not forget the truth!
ja, ich bin viel stärker, als ich je gedacht hab
Yes, I am much stronger than I ever thought!
ich entferne welke blumen
I remove withered flowers.
wieso siehst du so traurig aus?
Why do you look so sad?
was willst du von mir?
What do you want from me?
ich mag wollen oder nicht, ich muss den feind verfolgen
Like it or not, I must pursue the enemy.
ich bin nicht frei von dieser welt
I am not free from this world.
was willst du von mir?
What do you want from me?
ich mag wollen oder nicht, ich muss den feind verfolgen
Like it or not, I must pursue the enemy.
ich bin nicht frei von dieser welt
I am not free from this world.
egal wie hart du auch bist
No matter how tough you are,
fliege höher!
fly higher!
laufe viel schneller!
Run much faster!
du bist sehr stark
You are very strong,
du bindest einen blumenkranz
you bind a wreath of flowers.
wieso siehst du so traurig aus?
Why do you look so sad?
du bindest einen blumenkranz
You bind a wreath of flowers,
wieso siehst du so traurig aus?
why do you look so sad?
I've been here for over four years now
and I know my anniversary's a few weeks ago
but this got delayed because, you know, we're a little bit past anniversary now
- but this got delayed because, you know, we're a little bit past anniversary now.
But I haven't shown you my solo anniversary merchandise yet
So here we go, it is time. Ta-da!
Oh, what is this?
Yes, my merchandise is once again kind of kitchen-themed.
Now let's start with number one, the plate! Ta-da!
Isn't it nice? This is like the main illustration
with, you know, our little cute new outfit.
And you can eat all kinds of stuff on it.
You can eat pasta, or you can eat a burger, or some fries, or steak.
Yes, or maybe some fried eggs.
But if you're not really a fried egg kind of person,
we would go to next,
the egg cup! Yes, we have an egg cup!
Where you put in your favorite boiled egg.
How many minutes, guys? One, two...
What's your favorite like... I don't know how to say it.
Well, I like it like maybe six, seven minutes.
But of course, just like that,
that's not enough. We need some salt there,
and maybe even some pepper. Do you put pepper on it?
But for that, I got you covered!
We have salt and pepper shakers! Oh, what's so cute!
They are in the shape of an egg, but they're wearing the uniform!
What, the egg gets to wear a uniform? That's new.
Well, yeah, it's really cute. It's your choice on which one you put salt and pepper, I think.
But I think there's a more common way to do it, with how many holes it has.
Is it any cute? And last but not least, another kitchen-themed thing would be, ta-da!
The glass! Yes, we have a glass!
Wonderful, finally a glass.
Don't break it. Be careful with it, but in case you break it, maybe get some more of the plate, too.
And after the glass, we have one more thing... A voice pack! Yay!
I wrote the script, and I tried my best. I was riding it on the airplane, and the situation is also on an airplane.
So I was like, don't worry, it's not a situation that really happened to me, but maybe in your brain it really happened, just like for me.
I spilled like some tomato juice and so on on you. So isn't that kind of spicy? It might just be.
Besides that, we have for a full set an A5 clear file which has the main illustration on it, which I would love to have that, so make sure to get the full set to support me!
And now we're getting into the last phase, guys!
Don't you want to hear some Kiara again? I got you covered.
Last song, everybody. Are you ready? Dosu... Kiara!
ooh
na, na-na, na-na-na-na-na-na
oh no
fell into the abyss unknown
left me bleeding, heartless, all alone,
ayo, eyo
no control, ayo, eyo
don't you dare apologize
turn my back and felt a cold knife
listen up, 'cause here's some advice
you're out of time, way out of line
it's taking over
like a renegade
eye for an eye,
i'll make you cry
tearing it down, do just what i wanna
keep calling me a sinner
(know you think so)
chimer-ery-ery-era
(got me twisted)
(such a misfit)
taking the crown, now you're calling me king
you gonna hear 'em all sing
(now sing it)
chimer-ery-ery-era
(louder like that)
(make 'em all ah)
don't back it up, don't back it up, keep that aim
i got thoughts that will drive you insane
come over if you like
we'll have a lot of fun,
but i got a lot of bite
i do what i want, make sure you don't forget it
an army on my back, say i'm sick, i'm just sadistic
not living in a lie, pariah in the light
i wanna see the way you bleed
(the way you bleed)
it's taking over
like a renegade
eye for an eye,
i'll make you cry
tearing it down, do just what i wanna
keep calling me a sinner
(know you think so)
chimer-ery-ery-era
(got me twisted)
(such a misfit)
taking the crown, now you're calling me king
Taking the crown now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear 'em all sing
Chimera
I want it all, so give me some more
Flames burnt me up down into my core
Oh, you wished I'd stay down
but then I just rise
You're not my enemy
Baby, you're dead to me
Hear my voices screaming out loud, no doubt, yeah
La-la-la-la-la-la, Chimera
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Chimera
Taking the crown now you're calling me king
You're gonna hear 'em all sing
Chimera
La-la-la-la-la-la, Chimera
Kiara!
Responding to that again, huh? Did you press four?
Thank you.
So, the next song will actually be the last song,
but this one is very special because, for the first time ever, you'll hear my next song, MIRAGE!
And what's really special about this one is that, for the first time ever, I'm bringing in some back dancers, back dancers...
And what's really special about this one is that, for the first time ever, I'm bringing in some backup dancers—backup dancers
who are gonna join me, so please enjoy.
And afterwards, the MV will be released, so hopefully everything goes according to plan.
So please make sure to check that out too, and support my new song, MIRAGE!
Mirage!
Mirror's reflection, going under,
Confused obsession.
I still wonder if I was made for you,
if I could only see, oh please.
Make me up, a new persona calculated perfectly for you,
Pretending like it's all just for me? Don't think so, live life incognito.
Oh, I play god and yet I'm asking why,
You never see what I want, what I need, oh do you?
Oh do you?
Follow through, light you pursue, but now...
You sold me on a mirage,
I tore you up into shreds, I don't even know what to do with this mess,
Tell me the cost, sit, be good, play your part, my mirage.
Livin' with regrets, better left unsaid,
Thought I'd be the king and queen of newfound paradise, I'm beggin' you to see,
I'm you, you're all of me,
It seems like everyone wants it all around and around, running round and round on and on,
This cycle keepin' me captive,
You say I'm way too fragile,
I'm just your perfect idol.
Break me, shape me, I...
You never see what I want, what I need, oh do you?
Oh do you?
Follow through, light you pursue, but now...
You sold me on a mirage,
I tore you up into shreds, I don't even know what to do with this mess,
Tell me the cost, sit, be good, play your part, my mirage.
Spinnin' little lies, new disguise, on and on and on,
This mirage, I'm lost, who owns your heart? Mirage!
You make me fall in line,
You, you, no, ooh!
You sold me on a mirage
I tore you up into shreds
I don't even know what to do with this mess
Tell me the cost
Sit, be good, play your part, my mirage
Mi-mi-mimi-mirage you
Spinnin' little lies, new disguise, on and on
and on
This mirage, I'm lost
Who owns your heart? MIRAGE
Play your part, my mirage